# Mateusz Stankiewicz

#### Junior Front-end Developer

A highly motivated and reliable junior front-end developer with a passion for creating websites. Enjoy working as part of a team. Self-started, paying strong attention to detail. Eager to learn and develop knowledge and skills. Currently looking for a new and challenging position within a company where I could grow both personally and professionally. Come back home to Poland after six years spent abroad. Can work remotely.



- 🔀 mateuszstankiewicz999@gmail.com
- Białystok, Poland
- matthewstanki.github.io
- github.com/matthewstanki

- +48 728034680 (Poland) | +44 7548163066 (England)
- # 27 July, 1993
- in linkedin.com/in/mateusz-stankiewicz
- (instagram.com/matthewstanki

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# High reach FLT driver DMW Logistics

2016 - 2021

Sutton-in-Ashfield, England

 Loading and unloading materials from a variety of vehicles. Moving pallet-packed materials around the site or storage facility.
 Performing equipment checks and basic maintenance.
 Quality checking and counting stocks. Driving high reach FLT.

# Warehouse operative / Production worker (temporary work)

Freshstart Recruitment LTD / Senior Salmon Recruitment Agency

2015 - 2016

Nottinghamshire, England

 Work in various fast-paced environments such as Bonds Confectionery, Jigsaw Foods, Synseal Extrusions. Duties include picking and packing orders, loading and unloading goods from lorries, operating production line equipment, cleaning work areas.

## Bartender / Mixologist

**Pub Brama** 

2013 - 2015

Białystok, Poland

 Work in fast-paced and vibrant environment. Prepare and serve a range of alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks and cocktails. Keep the bar area clean and well stocked. Collect payment and operate tills.

## Material handler (part time)

Zinc Plating services

2013 - 2015

Białystok, Poland

Prepare materials surfaces using water or hazardous chemicals.
 Assist and maintain the zinc plating line production. Apply safe work practices and procedures at all time.

### **EDUCATION**

# University of Technology Białystok

Front-end Development

2014 - 2015

Białystok, Poland

 Web applications / Frontend Development

## **Secondary School No.7**

Language class

2010 - 2013
• English

German

Białystok, Poland

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**



#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

Portfolio (2020 - Present)

• https://matthewstanki.github.io

My Parallax Movie Project (2020 - 2021)

https://my-parallax-movie-project.web.app

My Arsenal Blog (2019 - 2020)

• https://arsenal-kanonierzy.web.app

LÓMË Premium Quality Sportswear (2018 - 2020)

• http://lome.azurewebsites.net

MatthewStanki99 School Project (2014 - 2015)

• https://matthewstanki99.firebaseapp.com

## **LANGUAGES**

#### Polish

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### English

Full Professional Proficiency

#### German

Elementary Proficiency

## **INTERESTS**

Creating websites Football Formula 1 Gym

MMA WW2 Techno Movies Video games